Tan Xue Wen, Rayner

Mobile : +65 9011 3793

Email : raynertanxw@me.com
Website : https://www.raynertan.me



Summary

Self-driven individual who is an adaptable learner. Possesses a strong analytical mind with good grasp of abstract concepts and a strong work ethic. Organized and meticulous. Experienced working in the Indie Game Industry as a Game Programmer. An avid reader, enjoying books like Clean Code and Design Patterns. Cares about the human touch, morals, and values. A people-oriented individual, involved in service, having served 2 years as a fulltime volunteer.

Work Experience

Volunteer Work (24th October 2019 – 24th October 2021)

- Fulltime volunteer for The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints, serving in the Australia Melbourne Mission.
- Served as the mission technology specialist, handling tech issues and support for 40 to up to 195 volunteers, scaling management corporate fleet of devices and solutions.
- Leader of 20-35 other fulltime volunteers, leading them in serving the community and working with various organizations to help those in need.

LandShark Games Pte. Ltd. (7th June 2019 – 6th September 2019)

- Full-time Game Programmer
- Developed new player profile system, working on both backend & frontend.
- Provided update support for current IPs, increasing product stability.

<< 2 years of National Service July 2017 – May 2019 >> LandShark Games Pte. Ltd. (24th October 2016 – 2nd June 2017)

- Intern Programmer
- Designed and built a reusable client-server caching system.
- Established Unity iOS build pipeline, writing various tools and plugins.
- Worked on many systems including asset management enhancements, debug tools and environments, new gameplay features for new IPs, etc.

Education

Temasek Polytechnic

2014 - 2017

Diploma with Merit in Game Design & Development [GDD]

- Awarded the Lee Kuan Yew Award for Mathematics and Science
- Course Gold Medal, with perfect cGPA of 4.0 (full score 4.0)
- Achieved 27 Distinctions in diploma subjects such as Advanced Game AI, Game Production and Publishing, Game Development Project, Game Math and Physics, Game Modeling, Graphics Programming, and Game Design.
- Received the Infocomm Media Development Authority (IMDA) Excellence Award, the Jurong Port Special Industry Price, the Jurong Port Project Prize, and the Jurong Port Prize.

School of Science and Technology, Singapore [SST] *GCE Ordinary Level Certificate*

2010 - 2013

- Achieved Top O-Level Performers award (2013)
- Awarded MOE Edusave Certificate of Academic Achievement (2013 & 2011)
- Received SST Achievement Award (2012 & 2011)
- Awarded North West Community Development Council Outstanding All Rounder Student Award – School Level (2011)

Project **Experience**

(Refer to website linked above for more project details)

Temasek Polytechnic

- Led team of 6, developed Tower Power, a Virtual Reality (HTC Vive), asymmetrical multiplayer game. Featured in showcase at Unite Singapore 2016. Main programmer for networking design and implementation. The game features hundreds of A* led enemy agents networked across clients. Tower Power was also awarded "Best Project" at TP InfoTech Day 2017.
- Developed Chessgeon in Unity Game Engine, a unique combination of card games and chess. Features optimized A* algorithms running on mobile.
- Led team of 4 in development of Cellulose, an action strategy mobile game involving 250 flocking-enabled AI cell units controlled in groups. Made with Unity Game Engine. Cellulose is a finalist in SiTF Awards 2016.

Personal Projects

Developed utility tools set for Unity Game Engine. Features flexible, quickly implemented animation functions for all GameObjects, similar to Apple's SKAction. Designed using Composite pattern.

Technical Skills

- Familiar with Design Patterns
- Proficient in Swift, C#, and C++ programming languages
- Experienced in Unity Game Engine, Xcode IDE, and SpriteKit frameworks
- Trained in Adobe Photoshop and Autodesk Maya

Achievements & Awards

- Singapore Computer Society IT Youth of the Year Award Finalist (2019)
- SiTF Awards Best Presenter & Project Special Mention Awards (2016)

Co-Curricular Activities

Temasek Polytechnic Game Design & Development Student Interest Group

- President (AY1516 AY1617)
- Executive Committee Member (AY1415 AY1617)
- Organized and held 3 school game jams
- Initiated and ran Unity, Gamemaker, and GIMP workshops for freshmen

School of Science and Technology, Singapore Information Communication **Technology Talent Development Program**

- Pioneer member and Secretary (2012 2013)
- Executed 3 EduCamps (unconferences discussing latest technology applications in the field of education) as part of the planning team

Miscellaneous Contributed to self-initiated service group, raising SGD\$4000 for Japan Red Cross to aid in disaster relief efforts after the 2011 Tōhoku earthquake.

Interests

Reading, origami, fountain pens, Chinese calligraphy, collecting collectables, art books, and game soundtracks, Pokémon, and plush toys. Also enjoys scenic views like those of Yosemite and Sakura Season in Shinjuku Gyoen. Also likes quiet time to reflect, ponder, and journal.

References

Paul Naylor Co-founder LandShark Games Pte. Ltd

Tel: +61 417 360 816

Managing Director

Pacific Basin Negotiators Pty. Ltd.

J Patrick Garth

Email: paul@landsharkgames.com